Guide to the Azalea Society of America Records
Azalea Society of America Records
1928-2013
1928 2013
Azalea Society of America
MC 00348
The Azalea Society of America records contain administrative information, chapter information, correspondence to and from the Society, membership information, various publications, and research files. Although items in the collection date back to 1928, the bulk of information falls between 1979 and 2013. This is an ongoing collection with publications added once available.
Created in 1979, the Azalea Society of America's goals include the promotion of the knowledge of and interest in azaleas and proper description and registration of azaleas. These goals are met through conducting studies of azaleas and providing a forum for azalea enthusiasts to discuss hybridizing, propagation, and culture of azaleas.
43.5 linear feet
North Carolina State University Libraries, Special Collections Research Center
Researchers may request copies of digital files. The Special Collections Research Center cannot guarantee that all files will open and will not in all cases have software available to read files.
Received from John Bearden Brown, 2002, 2006, 2007, and Frank Bryan, 2007; June 2011 (Accession 2011.0147); 2012 (Accession 2012.0016, 2012.0037, 2012.0091).
The records of the Azalea Society of America are organized into seven series: 1. Administration,2. Chapters,3. Correspondence,4. Members,5. Photographs,6. Publications,7. Research.
In 1979, a number of azalea collectors and hybridizers interested in sharing and improving the knowledge of azaleas founded the Azalea Society of America as a non-profit educational and scientific society. The Society's goals are to promote knowledge of and interest in azaleas; provide a forum for the sharing of experiences and the dissemination of techniques of hybridizing, propagation and culture of azaleas; promote the proper description and registration of new azalea hybrids and selections; conduct studies; communicate with the members through publications and meetings; and bring together all those whose interest in and appreciation of azaleas form a bond of friendship.
The Society has national officers and committees for overall structure and direction, along with a number of chapters to provide meetings, lectures, seminars, plant sales, auctions and exchanges, and fellowship at the local level. National membership includes membership in one of the local chapters, with At-Large affiliation for those members not joining a local chapter. Each spring, one of the local chapters hosts an annual convention to immerse members and friends in a long weekend of azalea activities at the national level. They feature tours of local gardens during the day, renowned speakers each evening, and ongoing sales of azaleas and companion plants.
There have been seventeen chapters (four are now defunct) in thirteen states: Alabamense (new in 2004), AlabamaBen Morrison (May 1980), MarylandBrookside Gardens (August 1979), MarylandDallas (May 1989), to be turned into Texas chapter, TexasDelmarva (May 1986), defunct, DelawareFlame (May 1984), defunct, South CarolinaLake Michigan (new in 2003), Michigan, Wisconsin, Illinois, Indiana, and other parts of the MidwestLouisiana (June 1981), LouisianaMobile (March 1983), defunct, LouisianaNorthern Virginia (May 1980), VirginiaNorth West (October 1983), appears to be in OregonOconee (November 1991), GeorgiaRalph W. Pennington (June 1981)Richmond (August 1979-December 1999), defunct, VirginiaRobert D. Gartrell (May 1980)Tri-State (October 1981), Illinois, Indiana, MichiganVaseyi (new in June 2001), North Carolina, South Carolina, Tennessee
The programs of the Society are designed to meet the needs of home gardeners, collectors and horticultural students, as well as nurserymen, hybridizers and landscape architects. Publications include an annual roster of members, and a quarterly journal, The Azalean, which is the Society's forum for members and others to share their observations on azalea culture, garden design, hybridization, propagation, new azaleas, and chapter activities.
The records of the Azalea Society of America document this organization, which is devoted to sharing and promoting the knowledge of azaleas, and date from 1928 through 2013. Included are materials documenting the founding of the horticulture society in 1979, its membership, and publications, as well as research on azalea culture, garden design, hybridization, propagation, and new azaleas.
The Administration series contains papers related to the administration of the Azalea Society of America. It includes the papers of the Board of Directors, Board of Governors, Executive Committee, by-laws of the national body, financial records, incorporation information, job descriptions, and procedures. The Chapters series is composed of materials, chiefly by-laws, relating to specific chapters.
Correspondence includes memoranda and electronic mail as well as postal mail sent to and from the Azalea Society of America. The early correspondence is chiefly among members of the Board of Governors concerning creation and amendments of the bylaws, incorporation of the society, formation of chapters, and the society's tax status. Throughout this series there are letters and memoranda about annual meetings, the society's finances, and membership. Also included are letters inquiring about membership in the society or requesting information about azaleas. Frequent correspondents are Ryon Page, William C. Miller, Robert Hobbs, Bob Stelloh, and William B. McIntosh.
The Members series contains materials related to the members of the Azalea Society of America. Members are broken down into groups: annual members, life members, new members, and overseas members. The Photographs series consists of photographs related to the society and includes about seventy photographs and six 35mm negatives of people, landscapes, and plants. People present include: Fred Galle, Betty Galle, George Harding, Joan Lerner, Milt Lerner, Ryon Page, Faith Page, and Ed Collins.
The Publications series contains issues of the journal of the Azalea Society of America, The Azalean, and related material; newsletters of the society's chapters; brochures distributed by the society; and publications of other organizations. The Research series consists of research notes documenting development of different hybrid varieties and correspondence related to this work. Also included are printed information regarding caring for azaleas, preparing azalea cuttings, different varieties of azaleas, garden design, and lists of azalea hybrids; surveys of and about azaleas; and scholarly articles about azaleas and rhododendrons, 1989-2002, most authored all or in part by Dr. Kathleen Kron.
Azalea Society of America; United States Azaleas; Research Azaleas; Azaleas; Photographs; Societies, etc. Horticulture; Varieties Azaleas; Rhododendrons; Periodicals Azaleas; Agricultural innovations; Publications; Periodicals; Plant breeding; Hybridization; Azaleas Breeding
- Administration, 1977-2013; 1977 2013; 8.7 linear feet
  This series contains papers related to the administration of the Azalea Society of America. It includes the papers of the Board of Directors, Board of Governors, Executive Committee, by-laws of the national body, financial records, incorporation information, job descriptions, and procedures. It is important to note that the Board of Governors changed in name to the Board of Directors in 1990. Additional incorporation files are housed in an oversized box.
  - Advertising for ASA, 1977-2006 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Alice Holland's ASA minutes for ASA meetings, 1977-1982 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - American Rhododendron Society conference, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Announcements of formation, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Annual Meeting. Agenda, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Annual Meeting. Agendas (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Annual Meeting. Convention Planning (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Annual Meeting. Finances, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual Meeting. History (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Annual Meeting. Joint Meetings. American Rhododendron Society (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Annual Meeting. Minutes (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Annual Meeting. Minutes, Correspondence and Brochures, 1998-2009 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Annual Meeting. Packets, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Meeting. Packets, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Annual Meeting. Packets, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Annual Meeting. Packets, 2002-2004 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Annual Meeting. Planning., 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Annual Meeting. Planning. Accommodations, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Annual Meeting. Planning. Correspondence, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual Meeting. Planning. Merchandise, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Annual Meeting. Planning. Name Badges, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Annual Meeting. Planning. Potential Conference Sites, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Annual Meeting. Planning. Speakers, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Annual Meeting. Planning. Tour, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Annual Meeting. Planning. Transportation, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Annual Meeting. Registrants, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual Meeting. Registrants (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Annual Meeting. Registration Forms (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Annual Report, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Applications for Membership in the Azalea Society of America, Brook Side Gardens Chapter, undated (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Articles of Incorporation (copy), 1979 (Legalbox 61, Folder 1)
  - ASA/BOD Teleconference Meetings, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    Copies of these Cassettes must be made prior to patron use.
  - ASA certificates. Item MC0034835001, 1980-2000 (Cardbox 62, Folder 1)
  - Azalea Society of America (ASA) Convention Report, Presidents Letter (newsletter), and Request for Review Comments for Spring 2006, 2001-2009 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - ASA Goals (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - ASA mailing analysis, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Azalea City Designation: Nacogdoches, Texas, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Azalea Society of America Convention, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Copies of this VHS tape must be made prior to patron use.
  - Azalea News Letter and Newspaper Aritcle, 2010-2011 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Azalea sales and expenses, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Azalea sales and expenses, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Azalea Sales and Expenses, 1994-1998 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Azalea Society Artifacts, 1979-2005 (Flatbox 63)
    2 Canvas Tote Bags, 1 Canvas Hat, 1 ASA License Plate, 1 Note pad with ASA logo, 1 ASA grey cotton T-shirt, 1 ASA corporate seal
  - Azalea Society of America Brookside Gardens Chapter (1 of ), 1979-1982 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Azalea Society of America Brookside Gardens Chapter (2 of 2) (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Azaleas See it All, The, undated (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors. Agenda, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors. Historical Value, 1997-2009 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors. Meeting Agendas, 1990-2002 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors. Meeting Agendas, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors. Meeting Minutes, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors. Meeting Minutes, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors. Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors. Meeting Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors. Meeting Minutes, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors. Meeting Minutes, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors. Members (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors. Voting Ballots (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors. Voting Proxies (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Board of Governors Meeting Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Board of Governors. [Misc.] (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Board of Governors. Committee Members (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Board of Governors. Elections. Nominees (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Board of Governors. Elections. Proxies (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Board of Governors. Elections. Results (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Board of Governors. Endowment Fund (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Board of Governors. Meeting Agendas, 1979-1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Board of Governors. Meeting Agendas, 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Board of Governors. Meeting Minutes, 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Board of Governors. Meeting Minutes, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Board of Governors. Meeting Minutes, 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Board of Governors/ Board of Directors Annual Meeting committee-related material, 1979-2005 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Business Documents, 2004-2007 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Bylaws, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bylaws, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bylaws, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bylaws, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Bylaws, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Bylaws, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bylaws. Amendments (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Bylaws. Drafts and Proposals, 1978-1979, 1984, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bylaws. Model for Chapters (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Comments on Board of Directors meeting issues, 1977-2006 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Committees. Azalea City Committee. Nacogdoches, Texas (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Committees. Executive Committee (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Committees. Executive Committee. Meeting Agendas (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Committees. Executive Committee. Meeting Minutes (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Committees. Finance Committee (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Committees. Membership Committee (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Committees. Membership Committee. Job Descriptions (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (1 of 3), 1992-2004 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (2 of 3), 1992-2004 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (3 of 3), 1992-2004 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Finances. Accounting Procedures (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Finances. Audits (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Finances. Banking. Bank Information (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Finances. Banking. Bank Statements, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Finances. Banking. Bank Statements, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Finances. Banking. Bank Statements, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Finances. Banking. Bank Statements, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Finances. Banking. Bank Statements, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Finances. Banking. Bank Statements (1 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Finances. Banking. Bank Statements (2 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Finances. Banking. Bank Statements (3 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Finances. Banking. Bank Statements (4 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Finances. Banking. Bank Statements (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Finances. Banking. Bank Statements (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Finances. Banking. Bank Statements (1 of 3), 1998-2000 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Finances. Banking. Bank Statements (2 of 3), 1998-2000 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Finances. Banking. Bank Statements (3 of 3), 1998-2000 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Finances. Banking. Bank Statements (1 of 4), 2000-2003 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Finances. Banking. Bank Statements (2 of 4), 2000-2003 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Finances. Banking. Bank Statements (3 of 4), 2000-2003 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Finances. Banking. Bank Statements (4 of 4), 2000-2003 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Finances. Banking. Cash Receipts, 1989-1996 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Finances. Banking. Check Registers, 1978-1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Finances. Banking. Deposit Tickets, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Finances. Banking. Deposit Tickets, 1988-1996, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Finances. Budget (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Finances. Budget. The Azalean (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Finances. Chapter Dues Transmittal List (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Finances. Deposit Totals, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Finances. Deposit Totals, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Finances. Deposit Totals, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Finances. Deposit Totals, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Finances. Donations (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Finances. Endowment Fund (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Finances. Expenses and Income (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Finances. Expenses and Income. The Azalean (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Finances. Final Fiscal Report, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Finances. Financial Reports (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Finances. History (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Finances. Invoices (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Finances. Membership Dues, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Finances. Membership Dues, Oct 1995-Mar 1996 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Finances. Membership Dues, Apr-Jun 1996 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Finances. Membership Dues, Jul-Dec 1996 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Finances. Membership Dues, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Finances. Membership Dues, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Finances. Membership Dues Notices, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Finances. Printing Bids (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Finances. Printing Costs (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Finances. Printing Costs. Brochures (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Finances. Printing Costs. Membership Rosters (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Finances. Printing Costs. The Azalean (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Finances. Receipts, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Finances. Receipts, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Finances. Receipts, 1988-1992 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Finances. Receipts. Postal (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Finances. Receipts. Telephone and Teleconferencing (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Finances. Taxes. Information (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Finances. Taxes. State (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Finances. Treasurer's Ledger. Deposits (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Finances. Treasurer's Ledger. Disbursements (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Finances. Treasurer's Ledger. Miscellaneous Accounts (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Finances. Treasurer's Ledger. Receipts (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Finances. Treasurer's Ledger. Treasurer's Reports (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Finances. Treasurer's Ledger. Worksheets for Reports (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Finances. Treasurer's Reports, 1981-1992 (Legalbox 6, Folder 1)
  - Finances. Treasurer's Reports, 1995-1997 (Legalbox 6, Folder 2)
  - Finances. Treasurer's Reports, 1998-2000 (Legalbox 6, Folder 3)
  - Finances. Treasurer's Reports, 2001-2002 (Legalbox 6, Folder 4)
  - Finances. Treasurer's Reports, 2003-2005 (Legalbox 6, Folder 5)
  - Frazier Columbia Nursery (1 of 3), 1976-1998 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Frazier Columbia Nursery (2 of 3), 1976-1998 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Frazier Columbia Nursery (3 of 3), 1976-1998 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Houston, Texas Application to Become a Certified ASA Azalea City, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Kehr Record Book and Azalea Society of America Files, undated and 2009 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    Copies of these CD's must be made prior to patron use.
  - Incorporation. Applications, 1980-1982 (Legalbox 6, Folder 6)
  - Incorporation. Applications for Reinstatement, 2002 (Legalbox 6, Folder 7)
  - Incorporation. Articles of Amendment (Legalbox 6, Folder 8)
  - Incorporation. Certificates (Legalbox 6, Folder 9)
  - Incorporation. History (Legalbox 6, Folder 10)
  - Incorporation. Literature (Legalbox 6, Folder 11)
  - Incorporation. State of Maryland (Legalbox 6, Folder 12)
  - IRS Corporate Reports, 1980-1987 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Letters of Resignation (Legalbox 6, Folder 13)
  - Logo Artwork, 1977-2006 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - McComb, Mississippi, Azalea City application, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Minutes of first meeting, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous, 1984-2007 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous News letter and Meetings, 2007-2009 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Monthly Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Monthly Reports, 1997-1999 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Monthly Reports, 2000-2001 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Monthly Reports, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Monthly Reports, 2003-2004 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Monthly Reports, 2005-2006 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Monthly Reports, 2005-2007 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Oconcge Chapter Formation Correspondence, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Officers, 1979-2005 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Officers and Committee Chairs (Legalbox 6, Folder 14)
  - Palatka, Florida Application to Become a Certified ASA Azalea City, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Policies. Azalea Collection (Legalbox 6, Folder 15)
  - Policies. Handling of Funds (Legalbox 6, Folder 16)
  - Procedures. Dues Collection (Legalbox 6, Folder 17)
  - Procedures. Mailing Process (Legalbox 6, Folder 18)
  - Satsuki Azaleas Program, 1983, undated (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Slide Collection Presentation (Legalbox 6, Folder 19)
  - South Gate, California Application to Become a Certified ASA Azalea City, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Tyler, Texas Application to Become a Certified ASA Azalea City, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Wilmington, North Carolina, Application for Azalea City Designation, 2009 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Wilmington, North Carolina, Azalea Festival Programs, 2007-2009 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Wilmington, North Carolina, Azalea Garden Tour, 2007-2009 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Wilmington, North Carolina, Beneath the Airlie Oak, undated (Box 71, Folder 8)
    Copies of this CD must be made prior to patron use.
  - Wilmington, North Carolina, Application for Azalea City Designation: Airlie: The Garden of Wilmington / by Susan Taylor Block, copyright 2001 The Airlie Foundation (Legalbox 75, Folder 1)
  - Wilmington, North Carolina, Application for Azalea City Designation: Belles and Blooms: Cape Fear Garden Club and North Carolina Azalea Festival / by Susan Taylor Block, published by Cape Fear Garden Club, 2004 (Legalbox 75, Folder 2)
- Chapters, 1980-2006; 1980 2006; 1.25 linear feet
  This series is composed of materials, chiefly by-laws, relating to specific chapters. Some papers are for chapters that no longer exist. However, not all remaining chapters are represented. Information about chapter membership may also be found in Series 3, Correspondence, or in Series 4, Members. Newsletters for the various chapters can be found in Series 6, Publications.
  - Albamense Chapter. Bylaws, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Albamense Chapter. Directory, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Ben Morrison, 1980-1990 (Halfbox 7, Folder 1)
  - Ben Morrison. Bylaws (Halfbox 7, Folder 2)
  - Brookside Gardens (Halfbox 7, Folder 3)
  - Brookside Gardens, 1980-1990 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Brookside Gardens. Azalea Mart, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Brookside Gardens. Azalea Mart, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Brookside Gardens. Azalea Shows, 1979-1993 (Halfbox 7, Folder 5)
  - Brookside Gardens. Bylaws (Halfbox 7, Folder 6)
  - Brookside Gardens. Chapter Press Clippings, 1980-1981 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Brookside Gardens. Membership (Halfbox 7, Folder 7)
  - Brookside Gardens. News Clippings, 1979-2005 (Flatfile 2)
  - Brookside Gardens. Ryon Page Memorial Gardens Layout, 1979-2005 (Flatfile 3)
  - Brookside Gardens. Show Tips, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Brookside Gardens. Test Report, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Dallas (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Dallas. Bylaws (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Delmarva (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Delmarva. Bylaws (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Delmarva. Finances (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Flame (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Flame. Bylaws (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Ben Morrison Chapter. 2004 ASA Convention. Item MC00348CD006 (Cardbox 62, Folder 6)
  - Louisiana (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Louisiana. Bylaws (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Louisiana Chapter: Correspondence, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Louisiana Chapter: Rochester, John, 1981-1987 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Mason-Dixon, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Mobile (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Mobile. Bylaws (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Northern Virginia (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Northern Virginia. Bylaws (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Northern Virginia. Meeting Attendees (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Northern Virginia. Members (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Northern Virginia. Members. Applications (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Northwest (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Northwest. Bylaws (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Pennington (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Richmond (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Richmond. Bylaws (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Robert D. Gartrell (Box 8, Folder 23)